<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
Copyright 2012 Damián Serrano Thode (@dsthode)

   Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
   you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
   You may obtain a copy of the License at

       http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

   Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
   distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
   WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
   See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
   limitations under the License.
-->
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hackful Reader</string>
    <string name="frontpage_feed">http://hackful.com/frontpage.rss</string>
    <string name="new_feed">http://hackful.com/new.rss</string>
    <string name="ask_feed">http://hackful.com/ask.rss</string>
    <string name="he_namespace">http://hackful.com/rss/hackful</string>
    <string name="btFrontpageTitle">Frontpage</string>
    <string name="btNewTitle">New</string>
    <string name="btAskTitle">Ask</string>
    <string name="btAbout">About</string>
    <string name="load_more_items">Load more items</string>
    <string name="open_dialog_title">Select action&#8230;</string>
    <string name="open_link">Open link Url</string>
    <string name="open_post">Open post Url</string>
    <string name="connection_error">Failed to get feed. Is your internet connection working?</string>
    <string name="about_dialog_title">About</string>
    <string name="about_dialog_text">
This application is a simple Hackful RSS feed reader, 
with access to frontpage, new and ask feeds, 
as well as Hackful post page and Hackful post link.\n
It was made by Damian Serrano Thode, and you can find my blog at 
http://dsthode.info and my Twitter stream at http://twitter.com/dsthode\n
\n
How to use:\n
--------------------------\n
\n
This application supports both tablets and phones, with different layouts for each one.
If you are on a tablet, you have a list of posts on the left side. Clicking on one will open
the post link on the right side, and with a long press a dialog will pop with two options: open post
link (the linked page in the post) or open post page (the Hackful post page).\n
If you are on a mobile phone, you will see just the list of posts, and by clicking on one the web browser 
will open and the post link will be loaded. If you make a long press, the same dialog with the same options 
as above will be shown.\n
On the right side of the action bar are the buttons to load each feed posts, and the frontpage is loaded 
by default on the application start\n
\n
What is Hackful?\n
--------------------------\n
\n
Taken straight from the page http://hackful.com/about :\n
\n
A place for European entrepreneurs to share demos, stories or ask questions.\n
\n
developed by @8bitpal\n
idea by @rayhanrafiq and @mattslight\n
hosting donated by incite ict\n
\n
Born out of the mailing list of a group called Open Coffee London, an 
amazing community of entrepreneurs helping each other everyday. \n
\n
We saw how open HackerNews is and thought we should give our European 
community more chance to flourish.\n
\n
Our next steps include\n
- Local Event Calendars: Both local and major European events, localised based on user settings.\n
- Local Angel Directories: Localised based on user settings.\n
- More sharing, subscription and data exchange options: Opt-in digest emails, JSON API and more.\n
\n
The source code for this platform is available on Github. 
Contributions, bug reports and reasonable feature requests are welcome.\n	
\n
We also hang out on IRC - #Hackful-Europe @ irc.freenode.net\n\n 
    </string>
</resources>
